Register of the Library of Social History Collection
Hoover Institution Archives
- Cuban Revolutionary Government Series, 1931-1992 (Box 200-248)
  - Issuances arranged by organization (Box 243)
    - Ministerio de Bienestar Social
      - Metas. No. 1-3, (1960) (Box-folder 245: 3)
      - Leaflet, 1960 (Box-folder 245: 4)
    - Ministerio de Defensa Nacional. Leaflet, n.d. (Box-folder 245: 5)
    - Ministerio de Educación. Pamphlets. Las cooperativas escolares; Discursos en Ciudad Libertad; Técnicas escolares modernas; Cria de conejos; En julio 26 como en enero 28, (1959) (1959) (1959) (1960) (1960) (Box-folder 245: 6)
    - Ministerio de Estado. Pamphlet. This Is the New Cuba, (1959) (Box-folder 245: 7)
    - Ministerio de Gobernació n
      - Gaceta oficial. Vol. 57 no. 11, vol. 58 no. 13 [agrarian reform and banking reform legislation], (1959) (1960) (Box-folder 245: 8)
      - Pamphlets. Legislación vigente de apliació n para los tribunales revolucionarios; Ley de procedimiento laboral, (1959) (1960) (Box-folder 245: 9)
    - Ministerio de Relaciones Exteriores
      - Boletín. No. 71, (1959) (Box-folder 245: 10)
      - Boletín cultural. No. 4, (1960) (Box-folder 245: 11)
      - Weekly News from Cuba. No. 1, (1961) (Box-folder 245: 12)
      - Pamphlets. La verdad de Cuba en las antenas del mundo; José Carrillo, Revolución y cultura; Guia y temario para jornadas martianas en Latino América; The Position of Cuban Sugar in the United States; Primero Congreso latinoamericano de mujeres; This Is the Truth / Esta es la verdad; El universo en Martí, (1959) (1960) (1960) (1960) (1960) (1960) (1960) (Box-folder 245: 13)
    - Ministerio de Salud Pública. Pamphlets. Juan Santos Fernandez, La vida rural; Desarrollo económico y salud en Cuba revolucionaria, (1960) (1961) (Box-folder 245: 14)
    - Movimiento por la Paz y la Soberanía de los Pueblos. Boletín. No. 2, (1961) (Box-folder 245: 15)
    - Movimiento Revolucionario 26 de Julio
      - Libertad. No. 5, (1960) (Box-folder 245: 16)
      - Razones. No. 7, (1959) (Box-folder 245: 17)
      - Sierra maestra. No. 1, no. 190, (1958) (1960) (Box-folder 245: 18)
      - Pamphlet. Económico de Cuba, (1959) (Box-folder 245: 19)
      - Leaflets, n.d. (Box-folder 245: 20)
    - Organización Latinoamericana de Solidaridad. Conference (1st:, 1967) (Box 246)
      - Preliminary issuances, including announcements and lists of participants (Box-folder 246: 1)
      - Speeches (Box-folder 246: 2)
      - Declarations (Box-folder 246: 3)
      - Press coverage, Cuban (Box-folder 246: 4)
      - Press coverage, Foreign (Box-folder 246: 5)
    - Organización Regional Interamericana de Trabajadores. Pamphlet. El movimiento sindical cubano bajo el régimen del Dr. Castro, (1960) (Box-folder 246: 6)
    - Organization of Solidarity of the Peoples of Africa, Asia and Latin America
      - Tricontinental Bulletin. N.n., (1966) (Box-folder 246: 7)
      - Pamphlets. René Anillo Capote, 25th Anniversary of the First Tricontinental Conference; Anti-Imperialism in Latin America, (1991) (n.d.) (Box-folder 246: 8)
      - Leaflets, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 246: 9)
      - Press releases, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 246: 10)
    - Partido Comunista. Printed and typed transcripts of articles, and clippings, 1931-1989 (Box-folder 246: 11)
    - Partido Obrero Revolucionario (Trotskista). Voz proletaria
      - No. 1-5/6, (1960) (Box-folder 246: 12)
      - No. 7-9, (1961) (Box-folder 246: 13)
      - No. 10, supp., 12, 14-16, (1962) (Box-folder 246: 14)
      - No. 20-22, 23 supp., 25, 27, 27 supp., 28-29, 31-32, n.n., 34, 39-40, (1963) (Box-folder 247: 1)
    - Partido Socialista Popular. Printed articles, 1946-1959 (Box-folder 247: 2)
    - Partido Unido de la Revolución Socialista. El orientador revolucionario. No. 79/80, (1965) (Box-folder 247: 3)
    - Prensa Latina. Panorama económico latinoamericano. No. 1, (1960) (Box-folder 247: 4)
    - Solidarity Conference of the Peoples of Africa, Asia and Latin America, (1966)
      - Preparatory bulletin (Box-folder 247: 5)
      - Proceedings (Box-folder 247: 6)
      - Press coverage, Cuban (Box-folder 247: 7)
      - Press coverage, Foreign (Box-folder 247: 8)
    - Unión Revolucionaria Comunista. Leaflet, 1941 (Box-folder 247: 9)
    - Unión Sindical de Artes Gráficas. Pamphlet. Milicias obreras gráficas, (1960) (Box-folder 247: 10)
    - United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization. Pamphlet. Report on the Method and Means Utilized in Cuba to Eliminate Illiteracy, (1964) (Box-folder 247: 11)
  - Issuances unclassified by organization
    - El avance criollo. No. 29, (1961) (Box-folder 247: 12)
    - Bohemia libre. Vol. 52 no. 11, vol. 53 no. 16, 28-29, 31, (1960) (1961) (Box-folder 247: 13)
    - Contemporary Issues. No. 50, (1965) (Box-folder 248: 1)
    - Cuba. N.n., (1961) (Box-folder 248: 2)
    - 10 de septiembre. No. 125, (1945) (Box-folder 248: 3)
    - The Independent. No. 147, (1964) (Box-folder 248: 4)
    - Solidaridad gastronómica. Vol. 9 no. 6, (1958) (Box-folder 248: 5)
    - Views and Comments. No. 40-41, (1961) (Box-folder 248: 6)
    - Pamphlets
      - Arthur Pincus, Terror in Cuba; Camilo Cienfuegos, heroe del pueblo; La tierra y la patria; Conjura contra Cuba en Caimanera; David Dellinger, America's Lost Plantation; Fermín Peinado, Beware, Yankee; La révolution agraire à Cuba socialiste, (1936) (1959) (1959) (1961) (1961) (1961) (1961) (Box-folder 248: 7)
      - René Dumont and Julien Coleou, La réforme agraire à Cuba; David Dellinger, What Is Cuba Really Like?; Jornada martiana, (1962) (1964) (1969) (Box-folder 248: 8)
      - Pablo Rojas, El centrismo de "tipo castrista" en América latina; José R. Murt Mulet, Carlos Borjas, un hombre de su pueblo; José Martí, La guerra social en Chicago; Nahuel Moreno, Dos metodos frente a la revolució n latinoamericana, (1979) (1990) (n.d.) (n.d.) (Box-folder 248: 9)
    - Printed articles and miscellany
      - Matthews, Herbert L. (By), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 248: 10)
      - Shapiro, Samuel (By and in response to), 1960-1962 (Box-folder 248: 11)
      - Agrarian reform (Re), 1959-1987 (Box-folder 248: 12)
      - Culture (Re), 1963-198 (Box-folder 248: 13)
      - Miscellany, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 248: 14)
- Nicaraguan Revolutionary Government Series, 1978-1991 (Box 249-254)
  Speeches and writings by leaders of the Nicaraguan revolutionary government. Arranged by author. Includes some additional material relating to Nicaragua.
  - Individual speeches and writings. Printed unless otherwise indicated.
    - Arce Castaño, Bayardo (deputy coordinator, Comisió n Ejecutiva, Frente Sandinista de Liberació n Nacional)
      - Speech re education, 1979 (Box-folder 249: 1)
      - Speech, 1979 October 1? (Box-folder 249: 2)
      - Speech upon visit of Organization of Solidarity of the Peoples of Africa, Asia and Latin America delegation, 1979 December (Box-folder 249: 3)
      - Speech, Universidad Centroamericana, 1980 July (Box-folder 249: 4)
      - Speech, anniversary of Nicaraguan Revolution, 1980 July (Box-folder 249: 5)
      - Speech re Nicaraguan Revolution, 1980 July (Box-folder 249: 6)
      - Speech, anniversary of death of Carlos Fonseca, 1980 November 8 (Box-folder 249: 7)
      - Speech to Asociación Nacional de los Educadores Nicaragüenses meeting, 1981 January 24 (Box-folder 249: 8)
        Spanish (printed) and English (typed transcript)
      - Speech, Encuentro Internacional de Solidaridad con Nicaragua, Managua, 1981 January 26 (Box-folder 249: 9)
      - Speech re U.S. intervention in Central America, 1981 March (Box-folder 249: 10)
      - Interview with Proceso (Mexico), 1981 March (Box-folder 249: 11)
      - Interview with H. Dieterich (North American Congress on Latin America), 1981 October or November (Box-folder 249: 12)
      - Interview with Freddy Balzán, 1982 May (Box-folder 249: 13)
      - Speech, May Day, 1983 May 1 (Box-folder 249: 14)
      - Speech, Congreso del Pensamiento Anti-imperialista, 1985 February 20 (Box-folder 249: 15)
      - Speech, Conference of Latin American and Caribbean Political Parties, Managua, 1986 February 13 (Box-folder 249: 16)
      - Speech to sugar workers, 1986 June 28? (Box-folder 249: 17)
      - Speech, Encuentro de Jovenes y Estudiantes Latinoamericanos y del Caribe, Managua, 1986 July 16 (Box-folder 249: 18)
      - Interview with John Bevan (British Committee in Solidarity with Nicaragua), 1986 (Box-folder 249: 19)
      - Interview with Excelsior (Mexico), 1987 June (Box-folder 249: 20)
      - Speech to representatives of Juventud Sandinista 19 de Julio, 1987 August 11 (Box-folder 249: 21)
      - Speech, anniversary of Russian Revolution, 1987 November 7 (Box-folder 249: 22)
      - Interview with Cuban journalists, 1987 November 20 (Box-folder 249: 23)
      - Interview with Barricada, 1988 February (Box-folder 249: 24)
    - Borge Martínez, Tomás (minister of the interior)
      - Biographical data (Box-folder 249: 25)
      - Speech, interment of remains of Carlos Fonseca, 1979 November 7 (Box-folder 249: 26)
      - Speech, 1979 December 12 (Box-folder 249: 27)
      - Interview with Organization of Solidarity of the Peoples of Africa, Asia and Latin America delegation, 1980 (Box-folder 249: 28)
      - Speech, anniversary of death of Augusto Sandino, 1980 February 20 (Box-folder 249: 29)
      - Speech, Women's Week, 1980 March (Box-folder 249: 30)
      - Speech to students, 1980 May 18 (Box-folder 249: 31)
      - Speech, Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional assembly, 1980 September 13 (Box-folder 249: 32)
      - Speech to Comisió n Interamericana de Derechos Humanos, 1980 October 10 (Box-folder 249: 33)
      - Interview with Julio Scherer García (Mexican journalist), 1980 November (Box-folder 249: 34)
      - Speech, anniversary of Partido Comunista, 1980 December 13 (Box-folder 249: 35)
      - Speech, Ministerio del Interior, 1980 December 27 (Box-folder 249: 36)
      - Speech to market sellers, 1981 January 15 (Box-folder 249: 37)
      - Speech re art, 1981 January 18 (Box-folder 249: 38)
      - Speech, Encuentro Internacional de Solidaridad con Nicaragua, Managua, 1981 January 30 (Box-folder 249: 39)
      - Speech, anniversary of death of Augusto Sandino, 1981 February 21 (Box-folder 249: 40)
      - Interview with Punto final (Mexico), 1981 June (Box-folder 249: 41)
      - Remarks on history of Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional, 1981 June (Box-folder 249: 42)
      - Speech, anniversary of Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional, 1981 July 19 (Box-folder 249: 43)
      - Interview with Tatiana Coll, 1981 July 21 (Box-folder 249: 44)
      - Speech, Universidad Autó noma de Puebla (Mexico), 1981 September 24 (Box-folder 249: 45)
      - Speech, Conferencia Permanente de Partidos Políticos de América Latina meeting, Managua, 1982 February 19 (Box-folder 249: 46)
      - Speech, May Day, 1982 May 1 (Box-folder 249: 47)
      - Speech, Conferencia Cristiana por la Paz de Latinoamérica y el Caribe congress, Managua, 1982 May 31 (Box-folder 249: 48)
      - Speech re conservation of Lago Xolotlán, 1982 June (Box-folder 249: 49)
      - Interview with Harrie Derks, 1982 August (Box-folder 249: 50)
      - Speech re women, 1982 September 29 (Box-folder 249: 51)
      - "Carlos Fonseca: Una síntesis de hombre y pueblo," Patria libre, 1982 November-December (Box-folder 249: 52)
      - Interview with Claudia Dreifus ( Playboy), 1983 (Box-folder 250: 1)
      - Interview with Alvaro Osorio Mejia (Colombian journalist), 1983 February (Box-folder 250: 2)
      - Speech re history of Frente Sandinista de Liberación Nacional, 1983 May 20 (Box-folder 250: 3)
      - Speech re Simón Bolívar, 1983 July 24 (Box-folder 250: 4)
      - Interview with Roberto Bardini ( Cuadernos del tercer mundo), 1984 February (Box-folder 250: 5)
      - Interview with Freddy Balzán, 1984 March (Box-folder 250: 6)
      - Speech, judicial congress, 1984 April 12 (Box-folder 250: 7)
      - Interview, 1984 May (Box-folder 250: 8)
      - Remarks to journalists, 1984 July (Box-folder 250: 9)
      - Speech re national television network, 1984 August 11 (Box-folder 250: 10)
      - Speech re state security, 1984 August 27 (Box-folder 250: 11)
      - Speech, anniversary of death of Carlos Fonseca, 1984 November 8 (Box-folder 250: 12)
      - Speech re radio communications, 1984 November 24 (Box-folder 250: 13)
      - Speech to teachers re anti-communism, 1985 January 19 (Box-folder 250: 14)
      - Interview with Bernardo Marques Ravelo, Havana, Cuba, 1985 April (Box-folder 250: 15)
      - Interview with Andrew Reding ( In These Times), 1985 May 5 (Box-folder 250: 16)
      - Interview with Pensamiento propío, 1985 June (Box-folder 250: 17)
      - Speech, Comisión de Autonomía de la Costa Atlántica conference, 1985 June 27 (Box-folder 250: 18)
      - Speech, Coloquio Nacional de Filosofía, 1985 July 6 (Box-folder 250: 19)
      - Interview with Pamela Jiles (Chilean journalist), 1985 August 13 (Box-folder 250: 20)
      - Speech, anniversary of Ministerio del Interior, 1985 October 17 (Box-folder 250: 21)
      - Interview with Luís Suarez (Mexican journalist), 1985 November 16 (Box-folder 250: 22)
      - Speech re volunteer police units, 1985 December 14 (Box-folder 250: 23)
      - Interview with Marta Harnecker re Atlantic Coast region, 1985 December (Box-folder 250: 24)
      - Interview with Panorama, 1985 December (Box-folder 250: 25)
      - Interview re Radio Católica, 1985 December (Box-folder 250: 26)
      - Interview with Marco Cantarelli (Italian journalist), 1986 January (Box-folder 250: 27)
      - Interview with Silvio Mora, 1986 February (Box-folder 250: 28)
      - Speech, Congreso Latinoamericano de Sociología, Rio de Janeiro, Brazil, 1986 March (Box-folder 250: 29)
      - Speech, 1986 April 17 (Box-folder 250: 30)
      - Remarks re Atlantic Coast region, 1986 April (Box-folder 250: 31)
      - "Playa Girón: Un salto hacia la vida," Bocay, 1986 April-May (Box-folder 250: 32)
      - Speech, symposium on Atlantic Coast autonomy, 1986 July 13 (Box-folder 250: 33)
      - Interview with Rodolfo Mattarollo (Peruvian journalist), 1986 July (Box-folder 250: 34)
      - Interview with Maritta Tkalec (East German journalist), 1986 August (Box-folder 250: 35)
      - Speech, anniversary of Comités de Defensa Sandinista, 1986 September 7 (Box-folder 250: 36)
      - Speech, meeting on prisons in Latin America, 1986 September 17 (Box-folder 250: 37)
      - Interview with Bocay, 1986 November (Box-folder 250: 38)
      - "Carlos Fonseca: Síntesis de hombre y pueblo," Barricada, 1986 November 7 (Box-folder 250: 39)
      - "Los origenes históricos y Sandino en la costa," Barricada, 1986 November 28 (Box-folder 250: 40)
      - Speech, Rubén Darío Day, 1987 January 18 (Box-folder 250: 41)
      - Interview with Juan Gargurevich (Cuban journalist), Havana, Cuba, 1987 March (Box-folder 250: 42)
      - Speech, Asamblea Multietnica, 1987 April 24 (Box-folder 250: 43)
      - Interview with Fredric Jameson ( New Left Review), 1987 July? (Box-folder 250: 44)
      - Speech during visit to Soviet Union, 1987 July (Box-folder 250: 45)
      - Speech, Day of Merriment, 1987 July 17 (Box-folder 250: 46)
      - Speech, De Cara al Pueblo public meeting, 1987 July 25 (Box-folder 250: 47)
      - "Revolutionary Nicaragua Tackles the Ethnic Question," World Marxist Review, 1987 August (Box-folder 250: 48)
      - Speech, Conferencia Centroamericana de la Mujer en la Ciencia, la Tecnología y la Medicina, 1987 August 26 (Box-folder 250: 49)
      - Speech re autonomy, Asamblea Nacional, 1987 September 1 (Box-folder 251: 1)
      - Speech, Asociació n Americana de Juristas conference, Havana, Cuba, 1987 September 14 (Box-folder 251: 2)
      - Interview with Pensamiento propío, 1987 September (Box-folder 251: 3)
      - Interview with Sergio Ferrari (Mexican journalist), 1987 November 4 (Box-folder 251: 4)
      - Interview with Arqueles Morales, 1987 November? (Box-folder 251: 5)
      - Memorandum re defection of Roger Miranda Bengoechea, 1988 January (Box-folder 251: 6)
      - Interview with Stephen Kinzer ( New York Times), 1988 February 7 (Box-folder 251: 7)
      - Speech, World Council of Indigenous Peoples meeting, Managua, 1988 February 11 (Box-folder 251: 8)
      - Speech, anniversary of death of Camilo Ortega, 1988 February 26 (Box-folder 251: 9)
      - Speech upon release of prisoners, 1988 March 27 (Box-folder 251: 10)
      - Interview with María Eugenía Camus (Chilean journalist), Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1988 April (Box-folder 251: 11)
      - Interview with Stella Calloni (Argentine journalist), Buenos Aires, Argentina, 1988 May? (Box-folder 251: 12)
      - Interview with El País (Spain), 1988 July (Box-folder 251: 13)
      - Interview with Orlando Oramas León (Cuban journalist), 1989 January (Box-folder 251: 14)
      - Interview with Carlos F. Chamorro B., 1989 March (Box-folder 251: 15)
      - Interview with Hortensia Campanella, Madrid, Spain, 1990 January (Box-folder 251: 16)
      - Interview with Leo Gabriel (Austrian journalist), 1990 January (Box-folder 251: 17)
      - Interview with Monserrat Sans (Chilean journalist), 1990 February (Box-folder 251: 18)
      - Interview with La Crónica, 1990 February (Box-folder 251: 19)
      - Interview with Oscar Madrid (Chilean journalist), Caracas, Venezuela, 1990 May (Box-folder 251: 20)
      - Interview with Irene Selser, 1991 May (Box-folder 251: 21)
      - Interview with Luís Suarez (Mexican journalist), 1991 August (Box-folder 251: 22)
    - Carrión Cruz, Luís (deputy minister of the interior)
      - Speech, 1979 September 8 (Box-folder 251: 23)
      - Interview with Jorge Timossi, 1979 November (Box-folder 251: 24)
      - Interview with Patria libre, 1980 September (Box-folder 251: 25)
      - Speech, 1981 January 10 (Box-folder 251: 26)
      - Interview with Freddy Balzán, 1982 November (Box-folder 251: 27)
      - Speech to educational brigade, 1984 February 12 (Box-folder 251: 28)
      - Speech, anniversary of Sandinista police, 1984 September 5 (Box-folder 251: 29)
      - Interview with Marta Harnecker (Chilean journalist) re Christianity, 1986 August 17 (Box-folder 251: 30)
      - Speech, Encuentro Latinoamericano de Organizaciones Comunales, 1987 February 21 (Box-folder 251: 31)
      - Speech, anniversary of Nicaraguan Revolution, 1987 July 17 (Box-folder 251: 32)
      - Interview with Sergio de Castro, 1990 June (Box-folder 251: 33)
      - Productores patriotas y la revolució n [pamphlet compendium of excerpts from speeches] (Box-folder 251: 34)
    - Núñez Tellez, Carlos (president, Asamblea Nacional)
      - Speech, Central Sandinista de los Trabajadores meeting, 1979 October 7 (Box-folder 251: 35)
      - Interview with Poder sandinista, 1980 January (Box-folder 251: 36)
      - Speech re mass organization, 1980 April 20 (Box-folder 251: 37)
      - Speech to journalism students, 1980 December 14 (Box-folder 251: 38)
      - Speech, Encuentro Internacional de Solidaridad con Nicaragua, Managua, 1981 January (Box-folder 251: 39)
      - "Unidad nacional," Patria libre, 1981 June (Box-folder 251: 40)
      - "'Una preocupación rondaba nuestras cabezas,'" Patria libre, 1982 June (Box-folder 251: 41)
      - Interview with Freddy Balzán, 1983 July (Box-folder 251: 42)
      - Interview with Barricada, 1984 June (Box-folder 251: 43)
      - Speech, inaugural session of Asamblea Nacional, 1984 November 4 (Box-folder 251: 44)
      - Interview, Mexico, Mexico, 1985 December (Box-folder 251: 45)
      - Speech, Asamblea Nacional, 1985 December 21 (Box-folder 251: 46)
      - Interview with Guatemalan journalists, 1986 April (Box-folder 251: 47)
    - Ortega Saavedra, Daniel (president)
      - Speech upon visit of President José Ló pez Portillo of Mexico, 1980 January 24 (Box-folder 251: 48)
      - "Nueva Guinea" [poem], 1980 January 24 (Box-folder 251: 49)
      - "Salisbury, 12 p.m." [poem], 1980 April 19 (Box-folder 251: 50)
      - "En matero" [poem], 1980 April 21 (Box-folder 251: 51)
      - Speech, anniversary of Nicaraguan Revolution, 1981 July 19 (Box-folder 251: 52)
      - Speech, United Nations General Assembly, New York, New York, 1981 October 7 (Box-folder 251: 53)
      - Interview with H. Dieterich (North American Congress on Latin America), 1981 October or November (Box-folder 251: 54)
      - Message to United Nations re U.S. military presence in Central America, 1982 March 20 (Box-folder 252: 1)
      - Speech, United Nations Security Council, New York, New York, 1982 March 25 (Box-folder 252: 2)
      - Speech, anniversary of Nicaraguan Revolution, 1982 July 19 (Box-folder 252: 3)
      - Speech, Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations regional conference, Managua, 1982 September 6 (Box-folder 252: 4)
      - Interview with Freddy Balzán, 1982 September (Box-folder 252: 5)
      - Interview with Playboy, 1983 (Box-folder 252: 6)
      - Speech, United Nations General Assembly, New York, New York, 1983 September 27 (Box-folder 252: 7)
      - Remarks re women in Nicaragua, 1984 September 28 (Box-folder 252: 8)
      - Remarks, press conference, New York, New York, 1984 October 2 (Box-folder 252: 9)
      - New Year's message, 1984 December 31 (Box-folder 252: 10)
      - Inaugural address as president, 1985 January 10 (Box-folder 252: 11)
      - Speech to Comisión de Autonomía de la Costa Atlántica, 1985 June 23 (Box-folder 252: 12)
      - Speech, anniversary of Nicaraguan Revolution, 1985 July 19 (Box-folder 252: 13)
      - Remarks to Central American delegates to World Youth and Student Festival, 1985 July 21 (Box-folder 252: 14)
      - Speech, Asamblea Sandinista, 1985 August 3 (Box-folder 252: 15)
      - Speech re new constitution, Asamblea Nacional, 1985 September 5 (Box-folder 252: 16)
      - Speech, United Nations General Assembly, New York, New York, 1985 October 21 (Box-folder 252: 17)
      - Speech to demobilized troops, 1985 December 2 (Box-folder 252: 18)
      - Message to United Nations re peace proposals, 1985 December 6? (Box-folder 252: 19)
      - Remarks, press conference re deployment of missiles to guerrillas, 1985 December 6 (Box-folder 252: 20)
      - Speech, De Cara al Pueblo public meeting, 1985 December 20 (Box-folder 252: 21)
      - Speech, Asamblea Nacional, 1985 December 21 (Box-folder 252: 22)
      - New Year's speech, 1985 December 31 (Box-folder 252: 23)
      - Remarks re agrarian reform, De Cara al Pueblo public meeting, 1986 January 11 (Box-folder 252: 24)
      - Interview, Guatemala, Guatemala, 1986 January 14-15 (Box-folder 252: 25)
      - Speech, anniversary of birth of Rubén Darío, 1986 January 18 (Box-folder 252: 26)
      - Remarks, De Cara al Pueblo public meeting, 1986 January 26 (Box-folder 252: 27)
      - Speech, De Cara al Pueblo public meeting, 1986 February 1 (Box-folder 252: 28)
      - Speech, Havana, Cuba, 1986 February 5 (Box-folder 252: 29)
      - Speech, Conference of Latin American and Caribbean Political Parties, Managua, 1986 February 11 (Box-folder 252: 30)
      - Speech, Asamblea Nacional, 1986 February 21 (Box-folder 252: 31)
      - Remarks during visit to Pantasma, 1986 February (Box-folder 252: 32)
      - Speech to Comités de Defensa Sandinista representatives, 1986 March 22 (Box-folder 252: 33)
      - Remarks, press conference, 1986 March 28 (Box-folder 252: 34)
      - Telephone interview with Rodrigo Wong Arevalo (Honduran journalist), 1986 April 3 (Box-folder 252: 35)
      - Message re peace proposals, 1986 April 12 (Box-folder 252: 36)
      - Remarks re peace proposals, 1986 April (Box-folder 252: 37)
      - Speech upon visit of José Figueres (Costa Rica), 1986 April 24 (Box-folder 252: 38)
      - Speech, De Cara al Pueblo public meeting, 1986 April 26 (Box-folder 252: 39)